A peer-reviewed journal that offers evidence-based clinical information and continuing education for dentists.

 [ Decisions in Dentistry - A peer-reviewed journal that offers evidence-based clinical information and continuing education for dentists.](https://decisionsindentistry.com/)

    [BISCO Adds New Flavors to its Line of FluoroCal 5% Sodium Fluoride Varnish with…](https://decisionsindentistry.com/2023/12/bisco-adds-new-flavors-to-its-line-of-fluorocal-5-sodium-fluoride-varnish-with-tri-calcium-phosphate/)

    [RevenueWell to Offer Synchrony’s CareCredit to its Dental Practices/Patients](https://decisionsindentistry.com/2023/10/revenuewell-to-offer-synchronys-carecredit-to-its-dental-practices-patients/)

    Prev Next

* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

decisionsindentistry.com; decisions.absorbtraining.com, (the “Site”) is owned and operated by Belmont Publications, Inc. (“Belmont”). We recognize the importance of privacy to you and are firmly committed to protecting your privacy when you visit the Site. As a result, we have instituted this website privacy policy (“Privacy Statement”), which applies only to the operation of the Site. Belmont is providing this notice to explain how we collect, use, disclose and protect the personal information that we collect from you in connection with your use of the Site. This Privacy Statement applies only to the use and collection of data collected by this Site and does not apply to any other data collected by us online or offline.

In general, you may visit the Site and view its content while remaining anonymous by not providing any personal information. **By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement and, if you provide us your personal information, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not provide us any information and do not use the Site.**

As used in this Privacy Statement, “we” includes Belmont, its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, and any third-party vendors we hire to assist in the administration of the Site, the collection, cataloging and/or analysis of data, and/or the processing or handling of any visitor transactions. These vendors are required to maintain the confidentiality of the user information and are prohibited from using it for any purpose other than as described in this Privacy Statement. Belmont is based in the United States, so any personal information we collect through this site will be transferred to and maintained in the United States. By using this Site and/or providing us with your personal information, you understand and agree that your personal information will be transferred to the United States and subject to disclosures and uses in accordance with U.S. law as described in this Privacy Statement.

### Registering with Belmont

In order to use certain services provided on or through the Site, you may need to register with us, which will entail your disclosure and transmission of certain information about you. In connection with your registration, or at any time after registering, you may “opt-out” or unsubscribe from receiving any communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions on the registration page, the Site or in any email you receive from us.

All materials posted, with the exception of materials posted in online discussions, are of a proprietary nature and subject to copyrights owned by the Belmont. Any reproduction, retransmission, or republication of all or part of any document posted on this site is expressly prohibited, unless Belmont has expressly granted consent on the web site page to reproduce, retransmit, or republish the material.

The names, trademarks, service marks, and logos of _Decisions in Dentistry_, _Decisions_ CE, or Belmont Publications, Inc., appearing on this site may not be used by another party in any advertising or publicity or be used to indicate sponsorship or affiliation with any service or product without prior express written consent from Belmont.

### Information We Collect

If you register with us, we shall collect certain personal information provided by you, which may include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, billing information, credit card or other financial account information, and certain other personal, professional and demographic information about you. Our Site may also collect non-identifiable information that becomes available to us as a result of your visit to our Site.

This information includes, for example, your IP address (a number automatically assigned to your computer when you visit the Site, and which is logged by our servers), your Internet Service Provider (“ISP”), your web browser, the type of operating system, the domain name of the website which links you to our Site, the pages you visited, the average time spent on the Site, and the products searched for on the Site. Because we are very interested in the successful dissemination of information through the Site, we will review visitor trends recorded on certain log files. In connection with such log files, analysis software will be used to generate reports that will allow us to determine how we can enhance your experience with our Site. This information will not be used to ascertain your identity or the substance of what you are viewing. The log files may be purged periodically, in our discretion, to maximize space on the server.

### Collection of Personally Identifying Information from or about Children

Belmont does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to Belmont. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under age 13, please contact us at [info@belmontpublications.com](mailto:info@belmontpublications.com).

### Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information

The information we learn from visitors helps us personalize and improve the Site and services that we offer through the Site. We use your information to respond to your requests for information and to generate and maintain mailing lists. We may also use your personal information for the following purposes: establishment and maintenance of our relationship with you; responding to your requests and inquiries; registering you for programs, events and/or services that you have requested; process, fulfill and follow-up on your applications and fee payments; meeting legal, regulatory, insurance, security and processing requirements; and otherwise with your consent.

### Other Uses

In addition, we may share your personally identifying information with any third-party, without your consent or approval and without notice to you, (i) as permitted or required by law, (ii) as incident to a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or similar event, (iii) under circumstances we believe reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety of our employees, users of the Site, or the public, (iv) to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our published policies, or (v) as is otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. From time to time, we may make individual User information available to carefully selected third parties to send Users information through e-mail or postal mail about their products or services. Belmont may also use and disclose any of your information when legally compelled to do so, or when Belmont, in good faith, believes that the law requires it or for the protection of Belmont’s legal rights or those of a third party.

### Cookies

We from time to time use cookies on our Site. Cookies are small text files that your web browser leaves on your hard drive to recognize you as a repeat user of our Site, track your use of our Site and target advertising. This allows for personalization of certain aspects of your visit to our Site. Information gathered from cookies in this way is only used on an aggregate basis. Unless a visitor specifically provides their identity to us, e.g., by registering at our Site, providing information through an online form or sending us correspondence from the Site, we will not know who the identification of individual visitors. We may use cookies to store preferences; record session information; develop information about Site visitors’ preferences and interests; record past activity at a website in order to provide better service when you return to our Site; or customize web page content based on information you voluntarily provide. You can disable cookies using your Internet browser settings. Please consult your browsers’ help function for information on how to disable cookies. Note that if you disable cookies, certain features of our Site may not function properly.

### Links

Our Site may contain links to other websites. Please recognize that we do not control these third party websites and this Privacy Statement will not apply to those websites. You should consult each applicable privacy policy before using another linked website.

### Security

We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we strive to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-parties from intercepting information. You should not assume or expect that any communication that you transmit to us (such as personally identifiable or other data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) is confidential. Belmont shall not be liable or responsible if any information about you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

### Access, Correction and Contacting Us

If you have questions about anything contained in this Privacy Statement, including how your personal information is used, if you wish to request that we correct, or change or remove any information about you that we may have collected, or if you wish to opt-out of receiving any communications from us, you may contact us at [info@belmontpublications.com](mailto:info@belmontpublications.com).

### Privacy Statement Changes

This Privacy Statement may be revised from time to time by us in our sole discretion. Any changes will be effective upon posting of the revisions at decisionsindentistry.com. We may post changes or modifications to referenced policies and guidelines without your approval, and may determine whether and when any such changes apply to you. Your use of the Site following our posting of any changes will constitute your acceptance of such changes. Should you not wish to be bound by the modified Privacy Statement, do not use the Site.

### Limitation of Liability

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, BELMONT SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES THAT ARE DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY RELATED TO THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE, OR RELATED TO THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, AND FUNCTIONS THEREOF, WHETHER GENERATED BY THE WEBSITE, BY ANOTHER USER, OR BY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOSS OF REVENUE OR ANTICIPATED PROFITS, LOST BUSINESS OR LOST SALES, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF INFORMATION, DISRUPTIONS OR DELAYS ON THE WEBSITE, THIRD PARTY ACTIONS TAKEN THROUGH THE WEBSITE, ACTIONS TAKEN RELATED TO YOUR ACCOUNT, MALWARE OR COMPUTER VIRUSES OBTAINED BY USING THE WEBSITE, OR LINKS ON THE WEBSITE) EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE TOTAL LIABILITY OF BELMONT IN RESPECT OF ANY MATTER TO WHICH THIS POLICY APPLIES OR REGARDING THE WEBSITE EXCEED ONE THOUSAND DOLLARS ($1000.00). Some jurisdictions do not allow certain limitations of damages so the foregoing may not apply to you.

### Jurisdiction and Venue

This Policy shall be subject to the laws of the State of California as apply to contracts entered into and performed in California between California residents and without regard to conflicts of laws principles. The State and Federal courts located in Orange County, California, shall have sole and exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute arising hereunder, and the parties hereby consent to the personal jurisdiction of such courts. The United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods is expressly disclaimed.

### Disclaimer

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. BELMONT MAY MODIFY THE POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME AND POST THOSE MODIFICATIONS HERE. BELMONT SHALL POST SUCH CHANGES AT LEAST THIRTY (30) DAYS BEFORE SUCH CHANGES BECOME EFFECTIVE, UNLESS SUCH CHANGES ARE IN RESPONSE TO A CHANGE IN LAW, JUDICIAL ORDER, OR AN URGENT CHANGE IN BELMONT ‘S BUSINESS, IN WHICH EVENT A SHORTER PERIOD MAY APPLY. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE AFTER ANY SUCH MODIFICATION CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE MODIFIED POLICY.

BELMONT PROVIDES THE WEBSITE AND ALL GOODS AND SERVICES ON AN “AS IS” BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY. BELMONT HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY, ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEAL, USAGE OR TRADE, AND INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS OR TITLE.

### General

Neither this Policy, nor any rights hereunder, may be assigned by operation of law or otherwise, in whole or in part, by you without the prior, written permission of Belmont. Any purported assignment without such permission shall be void. This Policy, including corresponding access to your General Information, Personal Information and Cookie Information, may be assigned by Belmont in whole or in part without notice. Any waiver of any rights of Belmont under this Policy must be in writing, signed by Belmont, and any such waiver shall not operate as a waiver of any future breach of this Policy. In the event any portion of this Policy is found to be illegal or unenforceable, such portion shall be severed from this Policy, and the remaining terms shall be separately enforced. Your use of the Website shall at all times comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations. This Policy is the entire agreement between the parties with respect to this subject matter, and supersedes any and all prior or contemporaneous or additional communications, negotiations or agreements with respect thereto. In consideration of your use of the Website, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Belmont (and Belmont’s officers, directors, employees, members, shareholders, managers, subsidiaries, affiliates, counsel, insurers, representatives, joint ventures, licensees and agents) from and against any and all claims, damages, threats, suits, proceedings, losses, liabilities and demands, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, arising from or related to: (i) your use of and access to the Website or any disclosure or unauthorized use of your user name or password; (ii) your violation of this Policy; or (iii) ) your violation of any law, regulation or the third party right, including without limitation, any copyright, property or privacy right. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive the expiration or termination of your use of the Website. You agree that: (i) the Website shall be deemed solely located in California; and (ii) the Website is and shall be deemed a passive website that does not give rise to personal jurisdiction over Belmont, either specific or general, in jurisdictions other than California. YOU AND BELMONT AGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION BY YOU ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THIS POLICY MUST COMMENCE WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES. OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.

### Effective Date of Policy

This Privacy Statement was last revised on and is effective as of September 1, 2017.

\- Advertisement -

[Load More](javascript:void(0);) [Follow on Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/decisionsindentistry/)

E-Mail Newsletter

"\*" indicates required fields

\*

 First Name Last Name

Email\*

State\*

AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific

CAPTCHA

Consent\*

 By signing up for our newsletters, you agree to our terms and privacy policy. \*

Consent\*

 By filling out this form you agree that Belmont Publications, Inc. and its partners may contact you via email about offers that may be of interest to you. \*

Δ

Current Issue

© 2024 - Decisions in Dentistry • All Rights Reserved.

ISSN 2380-1999

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. [Accept](#) [Read More](https://decisionsindentistry.com/privacy-policy/)

#### YEAR-END CE SALE

Coupon has expired

Get your units by year-end or buy now to get the discount and complete the courses next year. All at discounted pricing!

Get Special CE Savings!

\_\_\_\_

\_\_\_\_

Get Your FREE  
Local Anesthesia Tables!

Join our email list to download your free printable tables on local anesthesia, including: contraindications, allergies, impact of systemic health, anesthetic agents, and MRD for kids.

FIRST NAME:

LAST NAME:

EMAIL:

Thanks for Subscribing!

\_\_\_\_

\_\_\_\_

Please check your email and click the confirmation button so we can send you your free tables!

Sign in

Welcome, Login to your account.

[Forget password?](https://decisionsindentistry.com/ce/my-account/lost-password/)  Remember me

Sign in

Recover your password.

A password will be e-mailed to you.
